so now that we have seen how the one bit
history predictor Works let's do a quiz
about that so we have a one bit of
history and a two bit counter per
history and the pattern we will try to
predict is the not taken not taken taken
and then that repeats this is a regular
expression so pretty much it's not taken
not taken taken not taken not taken
taken Etc the one bit history is zero at
the beginning the two bit counters both
start start at the strong not taken
State and the question for you is after
a 100 repetitions of this pattern so
there are 300 outcomes nnt and that
repeats 100 times what is the overall
number of mispredictions that we will
have seen write that number here